A Guide to the Sealantic Fund Records FA265
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Urban Training Center for Christian Mission, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 431)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Urban Training Center for Christian Mission, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 432)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Urban Training Center for Christian Mission, June- December 1968 (Box 92, Folder 433)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Urban Training Center for Christian Mission, January-May 1968 (Box 92, Folder 434)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Urban Training Center for Christian Mission, 1965-1967 (Box 93, Folder 435)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Urban Training Center for Christian Mission, 1955-1964 (Box 93, Folder 436)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Vanderbilt University, 1965-1971 (Box 93, Folder 437)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Vanderbilt University, 1957-1964 (Box 93, Folder 438)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Vanderbilt University, 1952-1956 (Box 94, Folder 439)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Washington Theological Consortium, 1971-1973 (Box 94, Folder 440)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Yale University, 1965-1974 (Box 94, Folder 441)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: Yale University, 1952-1964 (Box 94, Folder 442)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: 1955 Newspaper Clippings, States A-M (Box 95, Folder 443)
- Theological Education in the U.S. Program: 1955 Newspaper Clippings, States N-W (Box 95, Folder 444)
- Miscellaneous: THEOLOGICAL U-TZ, 1955-1972 (Box 95, Folder 445)
- Miscellaneous: U, 1955-1972 (Box 95, Folder 446)
- United Theological Seminary, 1955-1971 (Box 96, Folder 447)
- Virginia Union University: School of Religion, 1961-1973 (Box 96, Folder 448)
- Miscellaneous: VA-VZ, 1955-1973 (Box 96, Folder 449)
- Miscellaneous: W-WER, 1955-1973 (Box 96, Folder 450)
- Miscellaneous: WES-WESTCHESTER L, 1955-1973 (Box 96, Folder 451)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Adoption Service of Westchester, 1961-1967 (Box 97, Folder 452)
- Westchester & Maine Program: American National Red Cross- Mt. Desert Chapter, 1962-1967 (Box 97, Folder 453)
- Westchester & Maine Program: American National Red Cross- Tarrytown Branch, Westchester Chapter, 1960-1965 (Box 97, Folder 454)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Arthritis Foundation- New York Chapter, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 455)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Boy Scouts of America- Katahdin Area Council, 1961-1967 (Box 97, Folder 456)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Boy Scouts of America- Washington Irving Council, 1962-1963 (Box 97, Folder 457)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Camp Sloane, 1966-1968 (Box 97, Folder 458)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Community Chest Association of the Tarrytowns, 1961-1967 (Box 97, Folder 459)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Family Service of Westchester, 1961-1967 (Box 98, Folder 460)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Family Service of Yonkers, 1961-1963 (Box 98, Folder 461)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Girl Scouts of America- Council of Abnaki, 1964-1967 (Box 98, Folder 462)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Golden Rule Society of the Union Congregational Church of Seal Harbor, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 463)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Town of Greenburgh- 175th Anniversary, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 464)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Maine Sea Coast Missionary Society, 1961-1970 (Box 98, Folder 465)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Mental Health Association of Westchester County, 1966-1972 (Box 98, Folder 466)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Mount Desert Island Child Guidance Association, 1961-1968 (Box 99, Folder 467)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Mount Desert Island Hospital, 1963-1967 (Box 99, Folder 468)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Mount Desert Island Public Health Nursing Association, 1961-1967 (Box 99, Folder 469)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Mount Desert Larger Parish, 1961-1967 (Box 99, Folder 470)
- Westchester & Maine Program: National Council on Crime and Delinquency- Westchester Citizen Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 99, Folder 471)
- Westchester & Maine Program: New York Association for the Blind- Westchester Lighthouse, 1953-1972 (Box 99, Folder 472)
- Westchester & Maine Program: North Tarrytown Fire Department, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 473)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Northeast Harbor Library, 1962-1967 (Box 99, Folder 474)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Phelps Memorial Hospital Association, 1961-1966 (Box 100, Folder 475)
- Westchester & Maine Program: School Union Number 98, 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 476)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Seal Harbor Village Improvement Society, 1961-1967 (Box 100, Folder 477)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Sleepy Hollow High School Parent-Teacher Association, 1964-1967 (Box 100, Folder 478)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Tappan Zee Mental Health Center, 1964-1967 (Box 100, Folder 479)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1965-1969 (Box 100, Folder 480)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1961-1964 (Box 100, Folder 481)
- Westchester & Maine Program: United Fund of Westchester, 1964-1967 (Box 101, Folder 482)
- Westchester & Maine Program: United Fund of Westchester, 1962-1963 (Box 101, Folder 483)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Urban League of Westchester County, 1966-1968 (Box 101, Folder 484)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Urban League of Westchester County, 1964-1965 (Box 101, Folder 485)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Urban League of Westchester County, 1962-1963 (Box 101, Folder 486)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Urban League of Westchester County, 1961 (Box 102, Folder 487)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester Children's Association, 1966-1968 (Box 102, Folder 488)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester Children's Association, 1961-1965 (Box 102, Folder 489)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester Council of Social Agencies, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 490)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester Council of Social Agencies, 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 491)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester Council of Social Agencies, 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder 492)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester Council of Social Agencies, 1961-1962 (Box 103, Folder 493)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester County Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Children, 1961-1967 (Box 103, Folder 494)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester Tuberculosis and Public Health Association, 1963-1967 (Box 104, Folder 495)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Westchester Tuberculosis and Public Health Association, 1961-1962 (Box 104, Folder 496)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Women's Civic League of Tarrytown and North Tarrytown, 1964-1967 (Box 104, Folder 497)
- Westchester & Maine Program: Young Women's Christian Association of White Plains and Central Westchester, 1962-1966 (Box 104, Folder 498)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript, Undated (Box 104, Folder 499)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript, Undated (Box 105, Folder 500)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript, Undated (Box 105, Folder 501)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript, Bound Copy, Undated (Box 105, Folder 502)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript, Bound Copy, Undated (Box 106, Folder 503)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Background Information- Chapter II Notes, Undated (Box 106, Folder 504)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Background Information- Chapter III Notes, Undated (Box 106, Folder 505)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Background Information- Chapter IV Notes, Undated (Box 106, Folder 506)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Background Information- Contributions to the Fund for Theological Education, Undated (Box 106, Folder 507)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Background Information- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 106, Folder 508)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Background Information- Sleepy Hollow Restorations, Undated (Box 106, Folder 509)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Background Information- Summaries of Theological Programs and Expenditures, Undated (Box 106, Folder 510)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Background Information-William Wing's Notes, Undated (Box 106, Folder 511)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Correspondence, Undated (Box 107, Folder 512)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: History of Sealantic Fund, Undated (Box 107, Folder 513)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: History of Sealantic Fund- Original Uncorrected Draft of Manuscript, Undated (Box 107, Folder 514)
- William Wing Sealantic Fund Manuscript: Literature, Undated (Box 108, Folder 515)
- Miscellaenous: WESTCHESTER M-WEZ, 1955-1972 (Box 108, Folder 516)
- Miscellaenous: WF-WZ, 1955-1972 (Box 108, Folder 517)
- YMCA of Bay Harbor and Mount Desert Island, 1966-1967 (Box 108, Folder 518)
- YMCA: International Committee, 1940 (Box 108, Folder 519)
- Younger Church Areas Survey of Protestant Theological Schools (Box 108, Folder 520)
- Miscellaneous: X-Z, 1957-1973 (Box 109, Folder 521)
- Application for Validation Certificate, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 522)
- Executive Committee: Corporate, 1948-1971 (Box 109, Folder 523)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 524)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 525)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 526)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 527)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 528)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1967 (Box 110, Folder 529)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 530)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 531)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 532)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1963 (Box 111, Folder 533)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1962 (Box 111, Folder 534)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1960-1961 (Box 111, Folder 535)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1959 (Box 111, Folder 536)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1958 (Box 112, Folder 537)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1957 (Box 112, Folder 538)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1956 (Box 112, Folder 539)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1954-1955 (Box 112, Folder 540)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1953 (Box 112, Folder 541)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 542)
- Meetings: Trustees- Corporate, 1945-1950 (Box 113, Folder 543)
- American Association of Theological Schools: Program and Reports- 28th, 29th, and 30th Bienniel Meetings, 1972-1976 (Box 113, Folder 544)
- American Association of Theological Schools: Summary of Proceedings- 21st Annual Conference, 1967 June 12-14 (Box 113, Folder 545)
- American Association of Theological Schools: Summary of Proceedings- 22nd Annual Conference, 1968 June 11-13 (Box 113, Folder 546)
- American Association of Theological Schools: Summary of Proceedings- 23rd Annual Conference, 1969 June 16-19 (Box 113, Folder 547)
- American Association of Theological Schools: Summary of Proceedings- 24th Annual Conference, 1970 June 15-18 (Box 113, Folder 548)
- American Theological Library Association: Summary of Proceedings- 25th Annual Conference, 1971 June 14-18 (Box 114, Folder 549)
- American Theological Library Association: Summary of Proceedings- 26th Annual Conference, 1972 June 19-23 (Box 114, Folder 550)
- Association of Theological Schools: Bulletin, 1970-1976 (Box 114, Folder 551)
- ATLA Index to Religious Periodical Literature, 1949-1952 (Box 114, Folder 552)
- Cambrindge Platonists, Undated (Box 114, Folder 553)
- Carter's Grove Plantation: A History, Undated (Box 115, Folder 554)
- Casebook on Church and Society, Undated (Box 115, Folder 555)
- Elizabethan Puritanism, Undated (Box 115, Folder 556)
- Ferdinand Christian Baur on the Writing of Church History, Undated (Box 116, Folder 557)
- Fund for Theological Educationg: Annual Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 116, Folder 558)
- Fund for Theological Educationg: Directory of Fellowships and Programs, 1954-1971 (Box 116, Folder 559)
- God and Incarnation in Mid-Nineteenth Century German Theology, Undated (Box 116, Folder 560)
- Horace Bushnell, Undated (Box 117, Folder 561)
- Index to Religious Periodical Literature: American Theological Library Association, 1960-1962 (Box 117, Folder 562)
- Index to Religious Periodical Literature: American Theological Library Association, 1963-1964 (Box 117, Folder 563)
- Index to Religious Periodical Literature: American Theological Library Association, 1965-1966 (Box 118, Folder 564)
- John Wesley, Undated (Box 118, Folder 565)
- Journal and Major Essays of John Woolman, Undated (Box 118, Folder 566)
- Lutheran Confessional Theology in America, 1840-1880 (Box 119, Folder 567)
- Melanchthon on Christian Doctrine, Undated (Box 119, Folder 568)
- Mercersburg Theology, Undated (Box 119, Folder 569)
- Oxford Movement, Undated (Box 120, Folder 570)
- Reformed Dogmatics, Undated (Box 120, Folder 571)
- Religious Index Rwo: Multi-Author Works, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 572)
- Seminary Survey, Undated (Box 121, Folder 573)
- Social Gospel in America, Undated (Box 121, Folder 574)
- Theological Education, 1964 Autumn-1965 Autumn (Box 121, Folder 575)
- Theological Education, 1965 Winter-1966 Summer (Box 122, Folder 576)
- Theological Education, 1966 Autumn-1966 Winter (Box 122, Folder 577)
- Theological Education, 1967 Spring-1967 Winter (Box 122, Folder 578)
- Theological Education, 1968 Spring-1968 Summer (Box 122, Folder 579)
- Theological Education, 1968 Autumn-1969 Spring (Box 123, Folder 580)
- Theological Education, 1969 Summer-1969 Winter (Box 123, Folder 581)
- Theological Education, 1970 Spring-1970 Autumn (Box 123, Folder 582)
- Theological Education, 1970 Winter-1971 Autumn (Box 123, Folder 583)
- Theological Education, 1971 Winter-1972 Summer (Box 123, Folder 584)
- Theological Education, 1972 Winter-1973 Autumn (Box 124, Folder 585)
- Theological Education Fund: Theological Book List, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 586)
- Theological Education Fund: Theological Book List, 1963 (Box 124, Folder 587)
- Theological Education Fund: Theological Book List, 1968 (Box 124, Folder 588)
- Theological Education Fund: Theological Book List, 1971 (Box 124, Folder 589)
- Theological Education Fund: Theological Book List, 1971 (Box 124, Folder 590)
- Architectural Drawings, 1957
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 591)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 592)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 593)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 594)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 595)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 596)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 597)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 598)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 599)
  - Interchurch Center-Blueprints Received from Beckonart, Separated According to Units of Operation, 1957 July 29 (Drawer I-1, Folder 600)
  - Interchurch Center-Plans for Expansion, Drawings, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder 601)
  - Interchurch Center-Plans for Expansion, Drawings, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder 602)
  - Interchurch Center-Plans for Expansion, Surveys, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder data_value_missing_d4678658a40cdeedfc97fc12e7e42b58)
  - Interchurch Center-Plans for Expansion, Surveys, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder 604)
  - Interchurch Center-Plans for Expansion, Surveys, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder 605)
  - Interchurch Center-Plans for Expansion, Surveys, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder 606)
  - Blueprints Found Within the Collection, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder 607)
  - Blueprints Found Within the Collection, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder 608)
  - Blueprints Found Within the Collection, Undated (Drawer I-1, Folder 609)
- Photographs, Undated
  - Miscellaneous Photos Found Within the Collection (Box 125, Folder 610)
  - Nursing Photographs, Undated (Box 125, Folder 611)
  - Sealantic Fund Photo Album, Undated (Box 125, Folder 612)